YOU DIDN'T SEEM TO MIND
SPENDING YOUR TIME
WITH THIS CRAZY GUY
WHOSE EYES WERE WIDE
OPEN FOR YOU
FOR A TIME WE HAD IT GOOD
I DID THE BEST I COULD
'TILL I LOST YOU ON THE WAY
AND I'LL FIND
SOME PEACE
THIS TIME I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WE'RE GONNA GROW
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU MY HEART
AND SOUL
THIS TIME THIS TIME
MY LOVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MAN
YOUR LOVER AND YOUR FRIEND
I'M GONNA LOVE YOU TRUE
I WANNA BE THE ONE
YOU COME HOME TO
I'M GONNA TREAT YOU RIGHT
I'LL DO YOU EVERY NIGHT
MY LOVE
SO WHEN I LOST MY WAY
COULDN'T THINK OF WHAT TO SAY
I WATCHED US FALL APART
THERE'S AN OPPORTUNITY
IT'S HERE FOR YOU AND ME
TO MAKE ANOTHER START
AND I'LL FIND
SOME PEACE
THIS TIME I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WE'RE GONNA GROW
I'M GONNA SHOW YOU MY HEART
AND SOUL
THIS TIME THIS TIME
MY LOVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MAN
YOUR LOVER AND YOUR FRIEND
I'M GONNA LOVE YOU TRUE
I WANNA BE THE ONE
YOU COME HOME TO
I'M GONNA TREAT YOU RIGHT
I'LL DO YOU EVERY NIGHT
MY LOVE
I WANNA BE YOUR MAN
YOUR LOVER AND YOUR FRIEND
I'M GONNA LOVE YOU TRUE
I WANNA BE THE ONE
YOU COME HOME TO
I'M GONNA TREAT YOU RIGHT
I'LL DO YOU EVERY NIGHT
MY LOVE